Ala Sudneva, Software Test Engineer

Wroclaw, Poland +48 518 029 29 7 | mailforalla@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ala-sudneva https://github.com/AlaSudneva

SUMMARY

Highly motivated Entry Level Software Tester with a foundation in manual testing, knowledge of testing procedures, creation of test documentation, Mobile, Web testing, DevTools, SQL knowledge and REST API testing. Previously worked as a wholesale sales manager in manufacturing and concurrently as a personnel specialist in the same company with around 100 employees. I have extensive experience in working with business management software, communicating with people, and resolving conflict situations. An effective communicator with attention to detail and strong teamwork skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

KAVpak LLC, Brest, Belarus, June 2013 - Sept 2014 Accountant/ personnel manager

- Worked with business management software, specifically the modules of 'Accounting', 'Personnel'.
- Introduced constantly developed the 'Personnel' module since it was not present before, which reduced document creation and processing time by 30%.

KAVpak LLC, Brest, Belarus, Sept 2014 – July 2023 Wholesale sales manager/personnel manager

- Introduced many features and enhancements to the 'Sales' module, helping to
 systematize the client database, simplify the process of price formation and document
 handling, easily generate reports, and conduct planning. This also reduced the time for
 document creation and processing.
- Implemented weekly sales plan forecasting, which increased sales volume by 20%.
- Established strict weekly control of accounts receivable reduced customer debt by 25%.

As an experienced user of business management software, I have a strong command of the business processes implemented in such type of software. This allows me to make the testing process more efficient and comprehensible.

EDUCATION

Brest State A.S. Pushkin University

Sep 2007 - Jun 2012

Faculty of foreign languages (English, German)| teacher of English, German Bachelor's degree

"Functional Software Testing" (course auth. Artsiom Rusau) Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

Functional testing

SKILLS

Test documentation (bug reports, checklists, test cases), mobile testing (Android studio, Charles Proxy), SQL knowledge (MySQL, MongoDB), REST API testing (Postman), web testing, HTML/CSS basics, Git and bash basics.